getsocial.io 2019-07-29

# Privacy Policy for Users Who Apply or Sign Up for a GetSocial Account

_The current privacy police was last modified on: 3/23/2016_

The following Privacy policy (“Privacy Policy”) applies to all services offered by GetSocial S.A. (“GetSocial”) via [https://getsocial.io](https://getsocial.io/) website and/or GetSocial applications and services (this set henceforth designated as "Site") to clients (“Clients”), including use of Site in their websites and/or apps (this set henceforth designated as “Clients Site”) and their users/customers (“End Users”) use of Site. 

This Privacy Policy describes how GetSocial collects and uses the personal information of Clients and End Users collected by using Site. It also describes how Clients and End Users can access and update this information. Please review our Privacy Policy below and let us know if you have any questions or concerns. 

The personal information collected through Clients (or its End Users) use of Site is shared with both the Client and GetSocial. By using Site, you consent to our privacy policy. 

GetSocial highly values the privacy of its Clients and End Users personal data and takes due care in processing and protecting personal data. Through its Site, GetSocial will process privacy, sensitive or personal data. We process data in compliance with the requirements of the Portuguese Data Protection Authority. 

* * *

## Terms and Conditions

Please visit also our Terms and Conditions section establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability ruling the use of Site. 

## What information do we collect?

We collect information from you when you register and use the Site. When registering on the Site you may be asked to enter your email address, complete name, credit card and/or other information if you decide to purchase and/or use a product or service. You may, however, visit our Site anonymously. 

GetSocial collects information under the direction of its Clients, and has no direct relationship with the individual End Users whose personal data it processes. GetSocial works with its Clients to help them provide notice to their End Users concerning the purpose for which personal information is collected. 

GetSocial does not process or store any Clients data regarding Payment Methods (like credit cards). 

## What do we use your information for?

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways: 

  * To personalize and improve your experience using the Site
  * To improve our the Site and provide better and more valuable services
  * To administer contests, promotions, surveys or other Site features
  * To publish content to third party sites like Facebook or Twitter
  * To send periodic emails

We may collect and process aggregated information that does not include Personal Information and we may otherwise disclose Non-Identifying Information and Log Data with third parties for behavioral advertising, industry analysis, demographic profiling, and other purposes. Any aggregated information shared in these contexts will not contain any Personal Information. 

## How do we protect your information?

The security of your personal information (Clients and End Users) information is important to us. When you enter sensitive information (such as login credentials or credit card information) we encrypt the transmission of that information using secure socket layer technology (SSL). 

We follow generally accepted standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, we cannot guarantee its absolute security. If you have any questions about security on our Web site, you can contact support [at] getsocial.io. 

## User Access and Choice

If your personal information changes, or if you no longer desire our service, you may correct, update, or delete by emailing our Customer Support at support [at] getsocial.io. 

We collect information for our Clients. If you are an End User of one of our Clients and would no longer like to be contacted by one of our Clients that use our Site, please contact the Client that you interact with directly. If you are a Client and would like to update or delete your account please contact us at support [at] getsocial.io. 

We will retain your information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you services. GetSocial will retain personal data we process on behalf of our Clients for as long as needed to provide services to our Clients. We will retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements. 

## Opt-out Preferences

If you wish to subscribe to our newsletter(s), we will use your name and email address to send the newsletter to you. You may choose to stop receiving our newsletter or marketing emails by following the unsubscribe instructions included in these emails or you can contact us at [support@getsocial.io](mailto:support@getsocial.io?subject=Privacy%20Policy%20Question). 

## Access and Choice regarding Data Controlled by our Clients

GetSocial has no direct relationship with the individuals whose personal data it processes. An individual End User who seeks access, who seeks to correct, amend, delete inaccurate data or withdraw consent to further contact should direct his/her query to the GetSocial Client (the data controller). If the Client requests GetSocial to remove the data, we will respond to their request within 30 days. 

## Do we use cookies?

Yes (cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser, if you allow that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information). We use cookies to understand and save your preferences for future visits and compile data about End Users Site usage, so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future. 

A cookie is a small text file that is stored on a user’s computer for record-keeping purposes. We use cookies on this site. We do not link the information we store in cookies to any personal information you submit while on our site. 

We use both session ID cookies and/or persistent cookies. A session ID cookie expires when you close your browser. A persistent cookie remains on your hard drive for an extended period of time. You can remove persistent cookies directly in your browser’s settings. Persistent cookies also enable us to track and target the interests of End Users to enhance the experience on Site. 

If you reject cookies, you may still use Site, but your ability to use some areas of Site, such as promotions, contests or surveys, will be limited. 

## Log Files/Tracking Service

As is true of most Web sites, we gather certain information automatically and store it in log files. This information includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, and clickstream data. We use this information to analyze trends, to administer the Site, to track End Users movements around Client Sites and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole. We do link this automatically collected data to cookies which are not considered personal information. IP addresses are not tied to personal information. 

We may share non-aggregate, non-personal Usage Information , including End Users segments, with third parties. We may use this information to provide advertisements, campaigns, promotions or other services about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to End Users. Information collected through this process may be used to influence which types of marketing messages End Users receive across Client Sites. We may also share aggregate statistical information about our services with third parties. We do not provide any personal information to these third parties. The possible use of cookies and pixel tags by these third-party advertisers, publishers, and ad networks are subject to their own privacy policies. We are not responsible for the information practices of these third parties. 

## Google Analytics Usage

This web site uses Google Analytics, a web analysis service of Google Inc. ("Google"). Google Analytics uses what are known as "cookies", text files, which are stored on your computer and make it possible to analyse the use of the web site. The data produced by the cookie concerning your use of this web site is usually transmitted to a Google server in the USA and stored there. In the event that IP anonymisation is activated on this web site however, your IP address will be abbreviated by Google within the Member States of the European Union or in other states which are contractual parties to the Agreement on the European Economic Area. Only in exceptional cases will the full IP address be transmitted to a Google server in the USA and abbreviated there. Google will use this information on behalf of the operator of this web site, in order to evaluate your use of the web site, in order to compile reports on web activities and in order to provide further services linked to use of the web site and of the Internet as regards the web site operator. The IP address of your browser, which is transmitted by Google Analytics, shall not be merged with other Google data. You can prevent the storage of cookies by configuring your browser software; however, we should like to point out that in this case it is possible that some of the functions on this web site may not operate to their full extent. In addition, you can prevent the data (including your IP address) produced by the cookie and related to your use of the web site being logged by Google and also prevent Google from processing this data by downloading and installing the browser plug-in available on the following link: <http://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout?hl=de.>

## Do we disclose any information to outside parties?

We do not share personal information of Clients to any third party. We may share End Users personal information with Clients and third parties only in the ways that are described in this privacy statement. If as an an End User you do not want us to share your personal information with these companies you may opt out or delete your account by contacting us at support [at] getsocial.io. 

We may provide or transfer your personal information to companies that provide services to help us with our business activities such as sending emails or offering customer service. Transfers to subsequent third parties are covered by the provisions in this Policy regarding notice and choice and the service agreements with our Clients. These companies are authorized to use your personal information only as necessary to provide these services to us. 

We may also disclose your personal information as required by law, such as to comply with a subpoena, or similar legal process when we believe in good faith that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights, protect your safety or the safety of others, investigate fraud, or respond to a government request to any other third party with your prior consent to do so. 

If GetSocial is involved in a merger, acquisition, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, you will be notified via email and/or a prominent notice on our Site of any change in ownership or uses of your personal information, as well as any choices you may have regarding your personal information, to any other third party with your prior consent to do so. 

## Supplementation of Information

In order to provide certain services such as demographic information to you, we may on occasion supplement the personal information you submitted to us with information from third party sources. 

We use the information to enrich our profiles of End Users. We tie this information to the personal information they have provided using Site. 

## Blog / Forum

Our Web site offers publicly accessible blogs or community forums. You should be aware that any information you provide in these areas may be read, collected, and used by others who access them. 

## Social Media Features:

Our Site may include Social Media Features, such as the Facebook Like button or the Twitter button. Social Media Features and Widgets are either hosted by a third party or hosted directly on our Site. Your interactions with these Features are governed by the privacy policy of the company providing it. 

## Login with Facebook

As an End User you can log in to our site using sign-in services such as Facebook or Twitter. These services will authenticate your identity and provide you the option to share certain personal information with us such as your name and email address. Services like Facebook give you the option to control how information about your activities on this Site are shared with others within your network. 

## Changes to our Privacy Policy

We may update this privacy statement to reflect changes to our information practices. If we make any material changes we will notify you by email (sent to the email address specified in your account) or by means of a notice on this Site prior to the change becoming effective. We encourage you to periodically review this page for the latest information on our privacy practices. 

* * *

## Contact Us

If there are any questions regarding this our Privacy Policy, you may contact us using the information below: [support@getsocial.io](mailto:support@getsocial.io?subject=Privacy%20Policy%20Question)
